Guide to the C-SPAN records, 1809, 1978-2012
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
- Series 1: Press Clippings (Boxes 1-51), 1978-2012
  - Alcee Hasting's Impeachment, July 10-August 3, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Nixon Resignation Special, Auust 8-12, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - House of Representatives, August 13-November 9, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Maine Day, August 29-September 14, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - C-SPAN-type Programming, August 29-December 6, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Virginia Gubernatorial Election, October 5-December 19, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Savings and Loan Hearings, October 31,-December 1, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Essay Contest, November 5-19, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Year End Programs, December 24-30, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Radio and Audio, 1990-1992 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Various, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Various, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Various, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Various, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Various, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Radio Simulcast, January 3-5, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - C-SPAN-like Programming, January 3-September 10, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Cable Programming, January 5-May 30, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - End of the Year, January 7-11, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Editorials, January 7-December 8, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - State of the State Speeches, January 8-15, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Terrorism Call-in Show, January 11, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Education, January 12-December 28, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Close Up America, January 15-December 7, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Congressional Coverage, January 21-November 17, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Letters to the Editor, January 27-November 29, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Courts, January 30-August 29, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - State of the Union, January 31, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Various, February 1-December 29, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - National Press Foundation Dinner, February 3-March 23, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Gubernatorial Debates, February 5-6, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Call-in Shows, February 9-December 5, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Prince Charles, February 22, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Cable World, February 25-October 15, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Ronald Reagan Testimony, February 26-March 24, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - American Profile, February 27-October 24, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - House of Commons, March 1-December 18, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Cable Programming, March 3-December 19, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - National Governor's Association Meeting, March 4-July 31, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Viewers, March 5-July 26, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Abortion Call-in, March 30, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - European Parliament, April 2-9, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - American Society of Newspaper Editors, April 4-6, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Earth Day Programming, April 11-20, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Athiests Convention, April 15, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Booknotes, April 15-May 5, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - U.S. Conference of Mayors, April 20, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - C-SPAN Update Newspaper, April 22, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - FCC Indecency, April 27, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - A Week in the Life of Talk Radio, May 18-August 15, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - U.S./U.S.S.R. Summit, May 27-June 15, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Cable Tiering, May 30-June 5, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Mideast Crisis, May 27-December 25, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Nelson Mandela, June 21-30, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Economic Summit, June 27-July 20, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Election 1990, June 28-November 18, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Japan, June 30-December 15, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Marion Barry Videotape, July 4-October 17, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Supreme Court, July 29-December 12, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Various, August-December 1990 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Dukakis Interview, August 3-11, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Boston Globe, August 6-7, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - David Souter Nomination Hearings, August 20-September 22, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - National Public Radio, September 5-7, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Channels, September 10, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Savings and Loan Hearings, September 23-24, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Multichannel News, September 24-December 10, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Call-in Show 10th Anniversary, September 27-October 20, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Budget Debate, October 8-November 15, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Use of C-SPAN Footage, October 11-25, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Saudi Arabia, October 15-December 3, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Sammons Communications Scholarship, October 15-December 12, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Ace Awards, October 19-November 19, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Keating Five Scandal, October 21, 1990-March 1, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Dwight Eisenhower Programs, November 11, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Various, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Various, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Various, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Various, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Various, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - USA Today, January 14-December 23, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Cable World, January 14-December 30, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - TV Guide, January 26-December 28, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Election's Media, January 28-November 18, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Broadcasting, January 28-December 2, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Cablevision, February 11-July 15, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Roll Call, February 14-December 9, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Los Angeles Times, February 34-October 30, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Multichannel News, February 25-November 22, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Presidential Campaign, March 15-August 19, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Various, March 17-December 18, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Washington Times, March 29-November 19, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Washington Post, April 19-December 26, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - NBC, Olympics, and PPV Carriage, Includes Correspondence, May 1-25, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - New York Times, May 24-December 27, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Associated Press, June 28-November 19, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Wall Street Journal, August 29-December 16, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - George H.W. Bush Interview, December 21, 1991-February 3, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Associated Press, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Board Member Press Clippings, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Board Member Press Clippings, August-November 1992 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Boston Globe, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Democratic National Convention-Part 1, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Democratic National Convention-Part 2, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Democratic National Convention-Part 3, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Election Coverage-Part 1, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Election Coverage-Part 2, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Esquire, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Los Angeles Times, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - National News Magazine, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - New York Daily News, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - New York Times, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Political Hotline, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Profiles and Feature Stories on C-SPAN, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Presidential Campaign, March 1992-February 1993 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Presidential Campaign, August-November, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Republican National Convention, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Roll Call, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - USA Today, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Various, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Various, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Various, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Various, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Various, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Wall Street Journal, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Washington Times, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Washington Post, January-June 1992 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - TV Guide, January 1992-January 1993 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Dan Quayle, January 5-October 22, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Cable World, January 13-October 19, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Broadcasting, January 27-October 19, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Cablevision, January 27-November 16, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - State of the Union, January 28, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Monitoring Times, February 1992 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Multivision, February 1992 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Multichannel News, February 10-December 7, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Electronic Media, February 17-March 2, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Variety, February 17-April 1, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Trade News Dailies, March 25-December 4, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Ross Perot Interview, March 29-August 4, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - NCTA National Cable Show, May 4-6, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Washington Post, July-December 1992 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Election 1992 Advertisements, July 12-26, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - School Bus Tour, 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Booknotes, 1993-2001 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Various, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Various, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Various, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Various, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Variety, January 7-April 2, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Electronic Media, January 11-February 15, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Oxford Program on Bill Clinton, January 13, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Sammons Communications and C-SPAN Scholarship, January 13-20, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Presidential Inauguration, January 13-29, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Cable Industry, January 15-November 21, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - American Profiles, January 17-December 28, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Letters to the Editor about C-SPAN, January 19-August 1, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Viewer Call-in Shows, January 26-February 23, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Audio Networks, February 1993 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Broadcasting, February 15-July 12, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Multichannel News, February 15-September 30, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Editorials about C-SPAN, February 23-December 23, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Television Viewing Survey, February 27-March 22, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Booknotes, February 28-July 4, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Education, March-June 1993 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Black Publications, March-August, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Coverage of the Legal System, March 22-April 12, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Cablefax, April 19-December 2, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Cable World, June 14-July 5, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Cable Vision, July 19-December 20, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Programming Highlights, August 2-October 3, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Special Order House Speeches, December 3, 1992-January 30, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - C-SPAN Cameras in Congress, 1994-1995 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - C-SPAN Cameras in Congress, 1994-1995 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Debates, 1994-1997 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Must-Carry/TC 1, 1994-1995 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Various, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Various, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - C-SPAN School Bus, September 9-December 31, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Newt Gingrich and Corporation for Public Broadcasting, December 25-27, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Various, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Various, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - About Book Series, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Big Press Kits, 1996-1997 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Book TV, 1996-2002 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Booknotes, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - C-SPAN3, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - C-SPAN Inauguration Coverage and Use of Real Video, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - C-SPAN Program Listings, 1996-1997 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - C-SPAN School Bus, 1996-2001 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Compliments on C-SPAN Programming, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Congressional Resources on the Internet, 1996-1997 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Free Air Time, May 6-June 25, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Leased-Access Proposal, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Letters to the Editor Demanding C-SPAN, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Must Carry, 1996-1997 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Must Carry, 1996-1997 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Must Carry, 1996-1997 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Must Carry, 1996-1997 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Must Carry, 1996-1997 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Presidential Campaign, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Presidential Campaign, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Presidential Campaign, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Presidential Campaign, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Presidential Campaign, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Republican National Convention-Part 1, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Republican National Convention-Part 2, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Republican National Convention-Part 3, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Republican National Convention-Part 4, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Republican National Convention-Part 5, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Various, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Various, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Various, January 1-May 9, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Government Shutdown, January 2-11, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - C-SPAN Scholarship Competition, January 2-December 28, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Editorials, January 3-April 22, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Various, January 4-May 25, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Presidential Campaign Programming, January 7-March 2, 199 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - C-SPAN Criticism, January 7-June 11, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - New Hampshire Primary, January 8-March 4, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Various, January 8-June 24, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Various, January 8-September 16, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Whitewater, January 8-December 1, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Third Party Presidential Campaigns, January 10-October 27, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - State of the Union, January 11-February 4, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - C-SPAN Bus Campaign Stops, January 11-May 1996 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Bill Clinton Campaign, January 14-June 23, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Articles on C-SPAN Employees, Board of Directors, and Brian Lamb, January 14-November 11, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Medicare Programming, January 23-June 12, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - State Campaigns, January 24-April 10, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Travelgate, January 29-May 10, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Campaign Websites, February 3-February 22, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Iowa Caucuses, February 4-April 6, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Republican Presidential Candidates, February 4-May 21, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Presidential Campaign, February 6-May 24, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Bob Dole, February 6-June 12, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Letters to the Editor on Presidential Campaign Coverage, February 9-March 6, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - State Presidential Primaries, February 18-March 28, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Various, February 26-November 1, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Louis Farrakhan Speech, February 27-March 10, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Presidential Election Debates, February 29-March 8, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - C-SPAN School Bus, March 7-October 18, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - C-SPAN Scholarship Competition, March 19-July 4, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Various, March 20-December 7, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Don Imus Speech at White House Correspondent's Dinner, March 22-May 22, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Abortion, April 17-October 12, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Political Party Conventions, May 2-August 26, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Network versus C-SPAN Campaign Coverage, May 26-September 18, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Televised Town Meetings, May 31-October 23, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Various, June 3-December 11, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Various, June 15-November 13, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Presidential Campaign, June 24-November 5, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Filegate, July 1-3, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - General Elections, July 3-December 4, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Democratic and Republican Conventions, July 5-September 4, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Democratic and Republican National Conventions, August 13-29, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Ross Perot and Reform Party, August 18, 1996-August 21, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Debates, September 6-October 27, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Senate Races, September 21-November 27, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Presidential Debate, September 25-November 4, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Negative Campaign Advertising and C-SPAN Footage, October 18-November 21, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Craig Livingstone, November 19-21, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Colin Powell Interview, November 21-December 19, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Bill Clinton Interview with Brian Lamb, December 16, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - About Book Series, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Booknotes, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Booknotes, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Booknotes Book-Part 1, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Booknotes Book-Part 2, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Booknotes Book, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Booknotes Website, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Brian Lamb and Booknotes, 1997-1999 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - C-SPAN Radio, 1997-2000 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Compliments on C-SPAN Programming, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Must Carry and Demand for C-SPAN, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - New Media, 1997-2000 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Senate Campaign Finance Hearings, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Streaming Internet Video, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Supreme Court, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Tocqueville Online, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Various, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Various, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Various, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Washington Journal, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Washington Journal, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Inauguration Coverage on the Internet, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Carriage of C-SPAN, January 8-August 26, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Bill Clinton Inauguration, January 10-25, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Washington Journal, August 30-November 5, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Booknotes Books, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Book TV in Depth, 1998-2004 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Daniel's Cablevision, California, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Frankfort Electric, Kentucky, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Supreme Court, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Various, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Various, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Various, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Various, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Washington Journal, March 7-August 24, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Digital Must-Carry, June 1-July 13, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Book TV on C-SPAN2-Part 1, June 1-October 30, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Book TV on C-SPAN2-Part 2, June 1-October 30, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Traveling Tocqueville's America, July 24-September 29, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Campaigns, September 24-October 11, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - American Presidents, Includes Correspondence and Public Relations-Part 1, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - American Presidents, Includes Correspondence and Public Relations-Part 2, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - American Presidents Series, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - C-SPAN Bus, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Steve Scully Class and Distance Learning, 1999-2004 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Various, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Various, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Various, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Various, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Various, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Various, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Various, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Various, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Various, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Book TV, 2000-2004 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Presidential Campaign, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Presidential Campaign, 2000-2001 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Various, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Various, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Various, January 2000 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Ranking Presidents and C-SPAN Bus, February 2000 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Various, March 2000 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Various, April 2000 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Various, May 2000 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Various, June 2000 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Various, July 2000 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Various, August 2000 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Various, August 2000 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Republican National Convention, August 1-3, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Various, September 2000 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Various, October 2000 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Various, November 2000 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Various, December 2000 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - American Writers Series, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Book TV, 2001-2003 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Book TV, 2001-2003 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Book TV Festivals, 2001-2003 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Brian Lamb, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - C-SPAN3, 2001-2003 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - C-SPAN Bus, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - C-SPAN Education Mentions, 2001-2004 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - C-SPAN-Hosted Educated Conference, 2001-2004 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - C-SPAN in the Classroom, 2001-2003 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - C-SPAN Radio, 2001-2004 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - C-SPAN Technology, Digital Upgrade, Engineering, 2001-2003 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Cable Center/Distance Learning, 2001-2003 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - International Coverage and Events, 2001-2002 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Letters to the Editor and Editorials on C-SPAN on Cable Service, 2001-2002 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Rob Kennedy, 2001-2004 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - September 11th C-SPAN Programming Mentions, 2001-2003 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Various, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Various, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Various, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Various, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - XM Satellite Radio, 2001-2002 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Various, April 2001 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Various, May 2001 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Various, June 2001 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Various, July 2001 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Various, August 2001 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Various, September 2001 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Various, October 2001 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Various, November 2001 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Various, December 2001 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - America and the Courts Series, 2002-2003 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Bill Clinton Presidency Course, 2002-2003 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Brian Lamb, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - C-SPAN2, 2002-2004 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - C-SPAN Bus, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - C-SPAN Employees, 2002-2004 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - C-SPAN.org, 2002-2003 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - C-SPAN Special Program and Series, 2002-2004 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - C-SPAN Video Archive, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Campaign in the Courtroom, 2002-2003 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Political Campaigns, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Susan Swain, 2002-2004 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Various, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Various, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Cameras at Zacerias Moussaoui Trial, January 2002 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Various, January 2002 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Los Angeles Carriage Problem, January 19-21, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Various, February 2002 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Various, March 2002 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Various, April 2002 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Various, May 2002 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Various, June 2002 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Various, July 2002 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Various, August 2002 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Various, September 2002 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Various, October 2002 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Various, November 2002 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Trent Lott and Strom Thurmond, December 2002 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Al Franken, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Antonin Scalia Citadel of Free Speech Award, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Book Expo America, Bill O'Reilly and Al Franken, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Brian Lamb, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Brian Lamb, 2003-2004 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Brian Lamb Awards and Honors, February 21, 2003-May 2, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 1)